

Bogoslavskyi Igor
Nationality:
Ukrainian
Family:
single
no children

Phone: +49 (152) 04471543 Address: Mirecourtstr. 12, 53225, Bonn Germany

On the Web: igor.bogoslavskyi@gmail.com LinkedIn::Igor Bogoslavskyi GitHub::niosus

> Facebook::bogoslavskyi G+::Igor Bogoslavskyi

Igor Bogoslavskyi

PhD Candidate

About me

I am a young computer science specialist, particularly interested in Robotics, Machine Learning and Computer Vision fields of study.

I am fond of the idea of autonomous moving vehicles and look forward to having a chance of facing the problems that arise in this field.

The best way to contact me would be just to send an e-mail.

Experience

May 2014 - Present, PhD candidate, Photogrammetry lab Rheinische Friedrich-Wilhelms University Bonn, Germany

 I am now a PhD candidate in the institute of Geodesy, Geoinformation and Cartography at the University of Bonn. My advisor is Prof. Cyrill Stachniss.

January 2012 - April 2014, Assistant, AIS lab Albert Ludwigs University of Freiburg, Germany

 As an assistant in the Autonomous Intelligent Systems lab at Uni Freiburg, I dealt with Kinect RGBD sensors mounted onto various platforms as well as unmounted, with relation to RGBD object segmentation and traversability analysis. Based on the developments in this project I have published a paper at the ECMR'13 conference.

June 2012 - April 2013, Assistant, HRL lab Albert Ludwigs University of Freiburg, Germany

As an assistant in the Humanoid Robots Lab at Uni Freiburg,
 I dealt with Kinect RGBD sensors mounted onto the NAO robot platform with relation to gesture analysis.

November 2011 - April 2012, Tutor, Image Processing course Albert Ludwigs University of Freiburg, Germany

- As a tutor in the chair of Computer Vision and Image Processing at Uni Freiburg my tasks were to help my fellow students to accomplish the course programming assignments.
- Involved c++ programming with relation to blurring/deblurring, optical flow and segmentation tasks.

December 2010 - October 2011, Junior Software Developer Timecode LLC, Kyiv, Ukraine

- worked as part of a team on a game for Android platform.
 Java Android programming, OpenGL.
- worked as part of a team on an Online Content Store controlled via Kinect sensor. C#.

Education

2011 - present, Albert-Ludwigs-Universitt Freiburg

MSc. Applied Computer Science

2007 - 2011, Kyiv National Taras Shevchenko University

BSc. Faculty of Cybernetics. Applied Math field.

Chair of Computational Methods

2004 - 2007, Lyceum 145, Kyiv

Higher basic education certificate, Mathematics, Physics.

Skills

Platforms and libraries

Linux
 OpenCV
 OpenGL
 Windows
 QT
 Android
 ROS
 OpenNI
 PCL

Programming and markup languages

- ∘ C++
 ∘ Matlab/Octave
 ∘ CMake
- JavaPythonSQLite

Projects

from October 2012, ROVINA Project

- ROVINA Robots for Exploration, Digital Preservation and Visualization of Archeological Sites.
- Traversability analysis based on depth images from Kinectlike sensor.
- Funded by European Commission.
- The corresponding paper was accepted to ECMR 2013 (European Conference on Mobile Robotics)

Publications

Efficient Traversability Analysis for Mobile Robots using the Kinect Sensor

- Presented at ECMR 2013
- The text of the paper can be found here:
 Efficient Traversability Analysis for Mobile Robots using the Kinect Sensor

Where to Park? Minimizing the Expected Time to Find a Parking Space

- To be presented at ICRA 2015
- An MDP based approach to minimize the expected time to find a parking spot and reach the goal by foot.

Honors and Awards

MINT Excellence Network Member

 I was chosen as one of 300 best applicants across Germany to the MINT Excellence Network. The candidates were chosen from the students who work in the fields of Math, Computer Science, Natural Sciences and Technic across Germany.

Trainings and Courses

CITEC Robotics Summer School

- Various presentations on robotics topic
- 5-day workshop on multi-sensoric data aquisition, focus on Kinect and eye-tracking cameras.
- https://www.cit-ec.de/

AI Course (Online)

o A course by Sebastian Thrun and Peter Norvig on AI.

AI for Robotics (Online)

o A course by Sebastian Thrun on Udacity.

CUDA Programming (Online)

Yet not finished course on Udacity.

Languages

- English (IELTS 8.0)
- o German (B2+)
- Russian (Native)
- Ukrainian (Native)

Fields Of Interest

- Autonomous Navigation
- Mobile Robotics
- Image Processing
- Computer Vision
- Machine Learning
- Planning Under Uncertainty
- Kinect
- SLAM
- Android Programming

Hobbies

- Android-programming (see my app: LearnIt)
- Photography
- Playing guitar

References

References upon request.

Igor Bogoslavskyi

Date: Signature: